<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-12-15T00:27:05+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">The journey of my life - Himanshu Kumar</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><author><name>Himanshu Kumar</name></author><entry><title type="html">The Meaning of life</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/the-meaning-of-life/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Meaning of life" /><published>2017-12-15T00:06:20+05:30</published><updated>2017-12-15T00:06:20+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/the-meaning-of-life</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/the-meaning-of-life/">&lt;p&gt;Hello Friends! This is my first ever blog. So, I think it would be good if I could introduce myself to you. I am Himanshu Kumar and 20 years old. I am an undergraduate student pursuing Information Technology at National Institute of Technology, Durgapur. I am too excited to finally start blogging but I wonder how long would I be able to keep this up. Yeah, I often start new things with so much enthusiasm but I am not able to keep it up for long. But I would try to keep this up for as long as I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my free time, I read online magazines and tech blogs. But to be honest, I still haven’t discovered what I truly like. I tend to spend time doing stuffs related to my academics and sometimes on social media. But sometimes I try to introspect myself and find true meaning of my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, the main motto behind starting this blog is that I want other people out there to know how did i face certain challenges that life constantly throws in my life. Sometimes, these challenges are so harsh that it often makes me think why do I even exist. Everyone takes birth and dies one day . Then what is the purpose of this life. In a population of 7 billion, do you think you have got some significance ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever you feel that way, remember that even though it is true that everyone who comes to this world dies, but it is the period between birth and death that gives the true meaning to ones life. It is you who gives the meaning to your life. Don’t go through life, grow through life and help others to make them know the true meaning of this beautiful life. Lets see, what tomorrow brings in our life.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Himanshu Kumar</name></author><category term="Blog" /><category term="Motivation" /><summary type="html">Hello Friends! This is my first ever blog. So, I think it would be good if I could introduce myself to you. I am Himanshu Kumar and 20 years old. I am an undergraduate student pursuing Information Technology at National Institute of Technology, Durgapur. I am too excited to finally start blogging but I wonder how long would I be able to keep this up. Yeah, I often start new things with so much enthusiasm but I am not able to keep it up for long. But I would try to keep this up for as long as I can.</summary></entry></feed>